Guide to the Richard M. Peabody Gargoyle Magazine collection, circa 1976-2009 MS2040
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Correspondence, 1977-1999; MS2040 Series 2
  - Author Correspondence, Jane Somerville, 1982-1990 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Author Correspondence, Derek Slade, 1982-1988 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Author Correspondence, Dave Slater, 1977-1985 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Author Correspondence, Zenon Slawinski, 1976-1978 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Author Correspondence, Howard Smead, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Author Correspondence, Dave Smith, 1983-1986 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Author Correspondence, Howard Smith, 1978-1983 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Author Correspondence, Rod Smith, 1984-1985 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Author Correspondence, Russ Smith, 1978-1982 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Author Correspondence, Willie Smith, 1981-1986 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Author Correspondence, Janet Snell, nd, undated (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Author Correspondence, Steve Sneyd, 1976-1983 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Author Correspondence, Anthony Sobin, nd, undated (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Author Correspondence, Bart Solarczyk, 1983-1989 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Author Correspondence, Stacey Sollfrey, nd, undated (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Author Correspondence, John Solt, 1983-1985 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Author Correspondence, Scott Sommer, 1983-1985 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Author Correspondence, Maya Sonenberg, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Author Correspondence, Frank Soos, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Author Correspondence, Ric Soos, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Author Correspondence, Laurel (& Marshall) Speer, 1980-1990 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Author Correspondence, David Spicer, 1982-1987 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Author Correspondence, David Spicer, nd, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Author Correspondence, Sharon Spencer, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Author Correspondence, Marilyn Stablein, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Author Correspondence, Patricia Haas Stanley, 1977-1985 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Author Correspondence, Martin Stannard, 1979-1985 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Author Correspondence, Candyce Stapen, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Author Correspondence, Donna Baier Stein, 1982-1986 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Author Correspondence, Eugene Stein, 1984-1989 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Author Correspondence, Jack Stephens, 1984-1990 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Author Correspondence, Gregory Stephenson, 1983-1989 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Author Correspondence, Marc E. Sterling, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Author Correspondence, Steve Stern, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Author Correspondence, Wendy Stevens, 1978-1982 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Author Correspondence, Andrew Stevenson, 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Author Correspondence, John Stickney, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Author Correspondence, W.C. Stickney, 1977-1984 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Author Correspondence, Carolyn Stoloff, nd, undated (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Author Correspondence, Brad Strahan, 1977-1986 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Author Correspondence, Peter Straus, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Author Correspondence, Silvana Straw, 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Author Correspondence, Belinda and S. Ramnathi Subreman, 1982-1990 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Author Correspondence, Ellen Summers, 1985-1988 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Author Correspondence, Ken Sutherland, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Author Correspondence, Ingrid Swanberg, 1981-1987 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Author Correspondence, The Swanns, 1981-1991 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Author Correspondence, Mary Smith, 1983-1988 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Author Correspondence, Graham Sykes, 1977-1985 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Author Correspondence, Michael Sykes, 1979-1989 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Author Correspondence, Marilyn Szabo, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Author Correspondence, D.E. Steward, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Author Correspondence, D.E. Steward, 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Author Correspondence, D.E. Steward, 1979-1981 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Author Correspondence, D.E. Steward, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Author Correspondence, D.E. Steward, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Author Correspondence, Elizabeth Tallent, 1977-1986 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Author Correspondence, Jeff Talmadge, 1976-1990 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Author Correspondence, Charles A. Taormina, 1978-1984 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Author Correspondence, Brian Tate, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Author Correspondence, Chuck Taylor, 1984-1986 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Author Correspondence, Dabrina Taylor, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Author Correspondence, Henry Taylor, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Author Correspondence, James Taylor, 1982-1986 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Author Correspondence, Pat Ellis Taylor, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Author Correspondence, Tetsuya, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Author Correspondence, Hilary Tham, 1988-1989 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Author Correspondence, Ken Timmerman, 1980-1987 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Author Correspondence, Kenneth Tindall, 1984-1989 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Author Correspondence, Benedict Tisa, 1984-1986 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Author Correspondence, Chris Toll, 1982-1986 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Author Correspondence, Cat Townsend, 1981-1986 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Author Correspondence, Mary M. Truitt, 1985-1991 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Author Correspondence, Sam Truitt, 1988-1989 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Author Correspondence, Donna Trussell, 1985-1990 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Author Correspondence, Donna Trussell, nd, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Author Correspondence, Donna Trussell, nd, undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Author Correspondence, Sarah Tuft, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Author Correspondence, Meg Tullock, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Author Correspondence, Rod Tulloss, 1975-1983 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Author Correspondence, Steve Tyler, 1988-1990 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Author Correspondence, Unknown, 1985-1987 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Author Correspondence, Lee Upton, 1982-1984 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Author Correspondence, Kevin Urick, 1976-1987 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Author Correspondence, Rita Valencia, 1982-1984 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Author Correspondence, Diana Vance, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Author Correspondence, Janine Vega, 1978-1990 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Author Correspondence, Ken Waldman, 1988-1989 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Author Correspondence, Rosmarie Waldrop, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Author Correspondence, Michael Walker, 1984-1986 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Author Correspondence, Jay Walsh, 1978-1983 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Author Correspondence, Mark Wamaling, 1983-1986 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Author Correspondence, Dave Ward, 1977-1982 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Author Correspondence, Barrett Warner, 1986-1989 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Author Correspondence, Kenneth Warren, 1980-1989 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Author Correspondence, Anna Watson, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Author Correspondence, Michael S. Weaver, 1982-1990 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Author Correspondence, Colin David Webb, 1978-1984 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Author Correspondence, Myles Weber, 1985-1988 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Author Correspondence, Ron Weber, nd, undated (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Author Correspondence, Jeffrey Weinberg, 1979-1986 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Author Correspondence, Susan Weinberg, 1985-1990 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Author Correspondence, Joel Weinstein, 1980-1989 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Author Correspondence, Sharon Weinstein, 1985-1986 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Author Correspondence, Dana Weimer, 1988-1990 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Author Correspondence, Carl Weissner, 1982-1984 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Author Correspondence, Mac Wellman, 1979-1985 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Author Correspondence, Bernard Welt, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Author Correspondence, Julia Wendell, 1982-1987 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Author Correspondence, Don Wentworth, 1981-1990 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Author Correspondence, William F. Van Wert, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Author Correspondence, Mary Wescott, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Author Correspondence, Dieter Weslowski, 1987-1989 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Author Correspondence, Tom Whalen, 1980-1988 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Author Correspondence, Gail White, 1981-1989 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Author Correspondence, Peter Wild, 1981-1988 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Author Correspondence, Sara Wildberger, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Author Correspondence, Charles Wilder, 1977-1983 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Author Correspondence, Michael Wilding, 1979-1987 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Author Correspondence, Michael Wilkerson, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Author Correspondence, Rick Wilson, 1978-1991 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Author Correspondence, A.D. Winans, 1979-1980 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Author Correspondence, Terence Winch, 1983-1986 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Author Correspondence, Valerie Wohlfeld, 1985-1987 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Author Correspondence, Reese Williams, 1984-1987 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Author Correspondence, Christopher Woods, 1983-1987 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Author Correspondence, Eddie Woods, 1981-1983 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Author Correspondence, W.C. Woods, 1980-1982 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Author Correspondence, James Wu, 1989-1990 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Author Correspondence, Aquin Mitsuo Yamagishi, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Author Correspondence, Tom Zigal, 1983-1986 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Author Correspondence, Thad Ziolkowski, 1982-1985 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Author Correspondence, Mary Kay Zuravleff, 1983-1990 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Keith Abbott, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Walter Abish, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Jennifer Allen, 1983-1984 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Julia Alvarez, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Sheila Ascher and Dennis Straus, 1982-1986 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Anna Banana, 1980-1990 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Carolyn Banks, 1981-1982 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Frederick Barthelme, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Martin Bax, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Peter S. Beagle, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Ann Beattie, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Lucia Berlin, 1989-1990 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Charles Bernstein, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Sallie Bingham, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Bill Bissett, nd, undated (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Michael Blumenthal, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Robert Boswell, nd, undated (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Paul Bowles, 1974-1986 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Marion Boyars, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Kay Boyle, 1978-1979 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, T.C. Boyle, 1980-1988 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Pete Brown, nd, undated (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Matthew J. Bruccoli, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Richard Burgin, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Tom Carson, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, George Chambers, 1982-1984 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Ann Charters, 1980-1989 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, J. Rives Childs, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, David Citino, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Andrei Codrescu, 1984-1986 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Wanda Coleman, 1984-1986 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Michael Collier, 1983-1985 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Dennis Cooper, nd, undated (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Judson Crews, 1983-1985 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Daniel Curley, 1983-1986 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Bruce Cutler, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Guy Davenport, 1977-1985 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Fielding Dawson, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, John Domini, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Rita Dove, 1982-1989 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Bruce Duffy, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Cornelius Eady, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Elaine Equi, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Roger Finch, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Roy Fisher, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Gene Fowler, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Candida Fraze, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Stuart Friebert, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 48)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Brendan Galvin, nd, undated (Box 29, Folder 49)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, George Garrett, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 50)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Daniela Gioseffi, nd, undated (Box 29, Folder 51)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Andrew Glaze, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 52)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Patricia Goedicke, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 53)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Philip Graham, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 54)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Joanne Greenberg, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 55)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Anthony Hecht, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 56)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Marcy Heidish, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 57)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Judith Hemschemeyer, 1984-1985 (Box 29, Folder 58)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, David Hilton, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 59)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Rolaine Hochstein, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 60)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, A.M. Homes, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 61)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Tim Hildebrand, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 62)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Colette Inez, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 63)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Josephine Jacobsen, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 64)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Tama Janowitz, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 65)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Charles Johnson, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 66)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Mary Jarrell, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 67)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Ted Joans, nd, undated (Box 29, Folder 68)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Hugh Kenner, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 69)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Ken Kesey, 1980-1986 (Box 29, Folder 70)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Jascha Kessler, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 71)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Faye Kicknosway, 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 72)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, W.P. Kinsella, nd, undated (Box 29, Folder 73)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Jerome Klinkowitz, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 74)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, John Knowles, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 75)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Joyce Kornblatt, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 76)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Allan Kornblum, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 77)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Robert Kotlowitz, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 78)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Jim Kouf, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 79)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Maxine Kumin, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 80)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Greg Kuzma, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 81)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Charles Larson, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 82)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, James Liddy, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 83)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Heather McHugh, 1989-1990 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Terry McMillan, 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Clarence Major, 1985-1986 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Bill Manhire, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Jay Martin, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Michael Martone, nd, undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - "Big Guns" Carol Maso, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Harry Mathews, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Paul Metcalf, 1982-1983 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - "Big Guns" Metzger, Deena, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Christopher Middleton, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Brown Miller, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Lawrence Millman, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - "Big Guns" Ursule Molinaro, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Harry T. Moore, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Lorrie Moore, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Faye Moskowitz, nd, undated (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Norm Moser, 1982-1988 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, G.E. Murray, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Opal Louis Nations, nd, undated (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Antonya Nelson, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Anais Nin, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, James Nolan, 1982-1983 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Desmond O'Grady, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Maureen Owen, nd, undated (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Claude Pelieu Washburn, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Jurgen Ploog, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Holly Prado, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Reynolds Price, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, David Ray, 1982-1986 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, F.R. Reeve, 1983-1990 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Kirk Robertson, nd, undated (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Edouard Roditi, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Samuel Rosenberg, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Susan Fromberg Schaeffer, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Bob Shacochis, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Roger Skillings, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Myra Sklarew, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Floyd Skloot, 1982-1988 (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, W.D. Snodgrass, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Anthony Sobin, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Maya Sonenberg, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Maura Stanton, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Sharon Sheehe Stark, nd, undated (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Michael Stephens, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Terry Stokes, nd, undated (Box 30, Folder 46)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Jonathan Strong, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 47)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Somtow Sucharitkul, nd, undated (Box 30, Folder 48)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Peter Taylor, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 49)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Robert Taylor, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 50)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Richard Thomas, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 51)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Molly Best Tinsley, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 52)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Barbara Unger, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 53)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, H.L. Van Brunt, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 54)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Rosmarie Waldrop, 1983-1987 (Box 30, Folder 55)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, David Foster Wallace, nd, undated (Box 30, Folder 56)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Lynd Ward, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 57)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Belle Waring, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 58)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Michael Waters, 1983-1990 (Box 30, Folder 59)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Bruce Weigl, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 60)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Jeffery H. Weinberg, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 61)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Ted White, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 62)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Mark Winegardner, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 63)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Ted Wilentz, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 64)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Michael Wilkerson, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 65)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Donald Winter, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 66)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Warren Woessner, 1979-1981 (Box 30, Folder 67)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Geoffrey Wolff, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 68)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Bill Zavatsky, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 69)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Paul Zimmer, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 70)
  - "Big Guns" Correspondence, Harriet Zinnes, 1982-1986 (Box 30, Folder 71)
  - General Correspondence, A, 1977-1991 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, B, 1976-1984 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, B, 1985-1988 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, B, 1989-1990 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, C, 1976-1985 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, C, 1986-1991 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, D, 1977-1984 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, E, 1978-1990 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence, F, 1976-1991 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, G, 1977-1991 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, H, 1976-1990 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, H, nd, undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, I, 1983-1991 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, J, 1977-1989 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, K, 1976-1990 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, L, 1976-1991 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, Mc, 1979-1991 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, M, 1969-1991 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, N, 1978-1990 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, O, 1978-1990 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, P, 1976-1990 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, Q, 1988-1990 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, R, 1976-1990 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, R, nd, undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, S, 1976-1984 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence, S, 1984-1989 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, S, 1989-1991 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, T, 1977-1989 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, U V, 1980-1991 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - General Correspondence, W, 1977-1990 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, X Z, 1976-1991 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Reference files, 1976-1993; MS2040 Series 3
  This series consists of publications and promotional literature collected by Peabody for referral, inspiration and potential use in his publications. Included are non personalized printed mailers, book catalogues, invitation cards, newsletters, event flyers and brochures that Peabody received from Washington DC libraries, bookstores, galleries, universities, museums and literary groups. As a well connected local literary figure, Peabody received invitations to many events.
  The documents publicize plays, announce poetry readings and advertise publisher's catalogs; however, several items also publicize concerts, art exhibits and film screenings. Although not a complete listing of cultural events in Washington DC, it is an excellent source for locating local arts and community related events in the city, many which Peabody attended. Additionally, there are literary publications, including journals, magazines, flyers, reviews, and individual works of short stories, original drawings and graphics from ca. 1976 to 1990. Many are products of small and local presses.
  - Arts Community Promotional Literature, A. B. Editions, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 1)